<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Peaceful.label>мирний</Peaceful.label>
  <Peaceful.description>Будуйте спільноту в режимі пісочниці.\n\nРекомендовано для гравців, які бажають зосередитися на аспектах будівництва спільноти у RimWorld.\n\nЦей режим вимикає основні загрози, але проблеми, такі як хвороби, психічні зриви та скажені тварини, все ще відбуваються.</Peaceful.description>

  <Easy.label>будівельник</Easy.label>
  <Easy.description>Будуйте колонію, відчуваючи дуз загрози.\n\n Рекомендовано для новачків у іграх цього типу, а також гравців, які бажають збудувати ідеальну колонію.\n\nВеликі загрози будуть слабшими, ніж у інших режимах. Деякі надзвичайні небезпеки вимкнені.</Easy.description>

  <Medium.label>середній</Medium.label>
  <Medium.description>Будуйте спільноту всупереч небезпекам.\n\nРекомендовано для досвідчених гравців у стратегії, які вперше грають у RimWorld, або для знавців гри, що потребують більше простору для реалізації своїх кумедних чи дивних цілей.\n\nТут буде простір для розвитку та процвітання, але планета все ж є небезпечною.</Medium.description>

  <Rough.label>грубий</Rough.label>
  <Rough.description>Strive to survive on a rough, tough planet.\n\nRecommended for: Players with experience with RimWorld, looking to play a rough story requiring skill to survive.\n\nThere will be good times and bad times; triumph and tragedy. It's all for the drama.</Rough.description>

  <Hard.label>дикий</Hard.label>
  <Hard.description>Face brutal survival challenges. The price of survival is blood.\n\nRecommended for: Experienced players who want to experience great tests and sacrifice.\n\nSucceeding at this level requires diverse strategies, disciplined preparation, and luck. Threats can spike and combine in vicious ways. Even if you play well, some challenges will be impossible to overcome without losses.</Hard.description>

  <Extreme.label>немилосердний</Extreme.label>
  <Extreme.description>Apply mastery of every RimWorld skill for just a chance to survive a harrowing trial against a merciless, unfair world.\n\nRecommended for: Experienced players who want to face a brutal, unfair challenge where even great skill may not prevent death.\n\nThis level is about dealing with losses, because preventing them is impossible. You'll spend a lot of time fighting wounded and recovering, and you'll need to sacrifice people and things you love. Unfair challenges and capricious death may come at any time.</Extreme.description>


</LanguageData>
