<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Mood.label>настрій</Mood.label>
  <Mood.description>Шкала настрою вказує наскільки ваш колоніст задоволений. Якщо показники стають занадто низькі, є ризик психічного розладу. В залежності від настрою, якщо стається психічний розлад, колоніст може сховатись на добу, або навіть когось вбити.</Mood.description>

  <Food.label>їжа</Food.label>
  <Food.description>Їжа - це кількість харчів, які нещодавно споживалися істотою. Якщо це в нулі, істота стає все більше голодною і в кінцевому підсумку помре.</Food.description>

  <Rest.label>сон</Rest.label>
  <Rest.description>Шкала сну вказує на те, скільки певна істота спала останнім часм. Якщо вона на нулі, істота може втратити свідомість.</Rest.description>

  <Joy.label>дозвілля</Joy.label>
  <Joy.description>Recreation is the need to have fun. Repeating the same kind of activity makes it less fun, so variety is necessary.</Joy.description>

  <Beauty.label>краса</Beauty.label>
  <Beauty.description>Beauty reflects how visually pleasing a person has found their surroundings recently. Beautiful things like art improve beauty when viewed, while ugly things like filth and rough stone surfaces reduce it.</Beauty.description>

  <Comfort.label>комфорт</Comfort.label>
  <Comfort.description>Comfort is gained by sitting in or sleeping on comfortable furniture. It is acquired while laying in bed, sitting in a chair while working, or other times.</Comfort.description>

  <Outdoors.label>outdoors</Outdoors.label>
  <Outdoors.description>Outdoors expresses the need not to be cooped up inside. It is harmed by long periods inside, especially underground. It improves when someone spends time under the sky, especially outdoors. It's not about the size of the rooms, but the need to be outside from time to time. Lack of outdoors time is a significant challenge for people who dwell in underground bases.</Outdoors.description>

  <RoomSize.label>room size</RoomSize.label>


</LanguageData>
